&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：让我们谈谈吊装。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Let’s talk about hoisting.
你们中有多少人以前听过这个短语？
How many of you have heard the phrase hoisting before?
好吧，它被抛出或被JavaScript抛出很长一段时间。
Okay, it is thrown around or has been thrown around JavaScript for a long time.
同样，变量提升，以及提升这个和提升那个。
As well, variables hoist, and hoisting this and hoisting that.
直到最近，也就是最近一两年，
Until recently, that is within the last year or two,
单词hoist实际上甚至没有出现在JavaScript规范中。
the word hoist literally did not even appear in the JavaScript specification.
因为事实证明吊装并不是真正的东西。
Because it turns out that hoisting is not actually a real thing.
JavaScript引擎不会提升，
The JavaScript engine does not hoist,
它不会按照吊装时所建议的方式移动东西。
it does not move things around the way it is suggested with hoisting.
吊装是我们编造的一个比喻。
Hoisting is a metaphor that we have made up.
这是我们制定的语言惯例，并且
It is a language convention that we have made up, and
我是说英语的惯例。
I mean English language convention.
这是我们编造出来讨论的英语惯例
It is an english language convention that we have made up to discuss
词汇范围的概念，而不考虑词汇范围，好吗？
the idea of lexical scope, without thinking about lexical scope, okay?
我会告诉你为什么它实际上不存在，为什么它真的不可能
And I'll show you why it doesn't actually exist, why it's really not even possible
对于它与这段非常简单的代码一起存在，它只需要几行代码。
for it to exist with this very simple piece of code, it only takes a few lines.
如果你试图解释一号线发生了什么，并且
If you try to explain what happens with line one, and
我们使用词汇范围讨论，就像我们已经讨论过的那样。
we use the lexical scope discussion like we already talked about.
然后，首先将其作为编译器传递，然后
Then you would first pass through this as the compiler, and
然后你将通过它作为一个执行。
then you would pass through it as an execution.
但人们似乎不喜欢做的事情，
But what people don't like doing, it seems,
从两次传球的角度来考虑这一点。
is thinking about this in terms of two passes.
人们似乎希望只经过一次就被困住了。
People seem to be wanting to be stuck on passing through it just once.
两次传球似乎更让人困惑，
Two passes seems more confusing,
只需给我一个单一通行证的解释就行了。
just give me an explanation that works with a single pass.
不管是真是假，我只是想要一个更方便的解释。
Whether it's true or not, I just want a more convenient explanation.
这就是吊装的来源。
And that's where hoisting comes from.
因为吊装说，好吧，我们可以解释这里到底发生了什么，
Cuz hoisting says, well, we could explain what really happens here,
如果有这种叫做提升的神奇行为。
if there was this magical behavior called hoisting.
也就是说，每当JavaScript的执行引擎进入一个作用域时，
Which was that any time JavaScript's execution engine entered a scope,
它神奇地向前看，发现所有的声明无处不在
it magically looked ahead and found all of the declarations wherever
他们在那个范围内，并为他们创造了变量，对吗？
they were in that scope, and made variables for them, right?
所以就好像JavaScript引擎找到那些变量声明和
So it's as if the JavaScript engine goes and finds those variable declarations and
在执行之前将它们移动到作用域的顶部。
moves them to the top of the scope before execution.
这就是字面上对吊装的描述。
That's literally how hoisting is described.
事实并非如此。
That's not what actually happens.
JavaScript实际上不会通过向上移动var来重新组织代码
JavaScript does not actually reorganize your code by moving the vars up
到了顶端，这里是我如何向你证明这不是发生的事情。
to the top, and here is how I can prove to you that that's not what happens.
因为，这种神奇的前瞻实际上是如何工作的？
Because, how would that magical look ahead actually work?
当它输入一段代码时，它是如何神奇地以某种方式
How would it magically somehow when it enters the piece of code for
在第一次通过的时候，就可以神奇地看到它
the very first time on the very first pass, magically be able to at it and
只找到那些声明？
only find that declarations?
当然不能使用正则表达式，因为JavaScript
You certainly can't use regular expressions for that, because JavaScript
是一种非正则语言，所以正则表达式还不够好。
is a non-regular language so regular expressions aren't good enough.
那么，你要怎么找出所有的VARS在哪里呢？
So, how are you going to figure out where all the vars are?
你要做一些非常复杂的处理
You're gonna do some very sophisticated processing
在该块中稍后出现的标记上，直到找到块的末尾。
on the tokens that come later in that block until you find the end of the block.
然后任何一个可能发生声明的地方，
And then any of those places where a declaration could have occurred,
然后你可以把它们拉出来，理论上你可以重新排列和移动它们。
then you can pull those out, and you could theoretically rearrange and move those.
猜猜这种神奇的，奇特的处理会被称为什么？
And guess what that magical, fancy processing would be called?
解析，好吗？
Parsing, okay?
这叫做解析。
That's called parsing.
如果你想在块的下面找到变量声明，
If you wanna find the variable declarations further down in the block,
唯一可以做到这一点的方法是解析。
the only way you can do that is with parsing.
所以吊装并不是真正的东西，它是一种速记，一种我们可以用来
So hoisting isn't really a thing, it is a shorthand, a convention that we can use to
尝试在不需要进入细节的情况下描述某事。
try to describe something without needing to get into the nitty-gritty details.
我并不是说这是一件坏事，而是一件相当普遍的事情，
I'm not saying that it is a bad thing but what has been rather prevalent,
正如我所看到的，在，我甚至数不清有多少堆栈溢出。
as I have seen, in, I can't even count how many Stack Overflow.
当人们问到JavaScript为什么要做某事时
When people asks questions about why JavaScript is doing something and
它看起来很奇怪或者坏了，他们发布了一些代码示例。
it seems like it's weird or broken, and they post some code example.
然后有人说，嗯，这是因为吊装，然后
And then somebody says, well, it's because of the hoisting, and
然后这个人说，好的。
then this person says, Okay.
结果发现他们只是错了。
And then it turns out that they're just wrong.
这可能会让你感到惊讶，但是
This may be surprising to you, but
你知道Stack overflow上的东西是错的吗？
did you know that stuff is wrong on Stack Overflow?
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：[听不到]。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: [INAUDIBLE].
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的，令人震惊，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yes, shocking,
我应该在扔知识炸弹之前给你警告的。
I should have given you warning before dropping that knowledge bomb.
这是一个事实，有关于Stack overflow的帖子，人们有
This is a fact, there are posts on Stack Overflow where people have
问了关于我的书的问题，你不知道JS的书。
asked questions about my books, the You Don't Know JS books.
在其中一个帖子上，很多帖子，但是在我发现的其中一个帖子上，
And on one of those posts, many of them, but on one of these posts that I found,
这个人说，凯尔在什么时候是什么意思
this person said, what does Kyle mean when, and
他引用了我在书中提到的一些段落。
he quoted some passage that I was talking about in my book.
我尽可能在Stack overflow上尝试进入并检查这些，但是
I try as much as possible on Stack Overflow to go in and check for these, but
太多了，我已经忘记了分类问题，
there's too many and I have lost track of triaging questions on,
已经被标记为你不知道JS或YDKJS。
that have been tagged with You Don't Know JS, or YDKJS.
所以，我遇到了这个帖子-一次，这就是这个问题。
So, I ran across this post-one time, and so here's this question.
我是写这本书的人，我的名字在书上。
And I'm the one that wrote the book, my name is on the book.
在这个星球上，没有人在什么事情上更具权威性
There is nobody on the planet that is more authoritative on the question of what did
我是说比我更好。
I mean than me.
&gt；&gt；演讲者2：[笑]&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我们能同意这一点吗？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [LAUGH] &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Can we agree with that?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：很好的观点。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Good point, there.
凯尔·辛普森：好吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay?
关于JavaScript我是否错了是另一个问题，但是
Whether I'm wrong about JavaScript is a separate issue, but
我的意思是，我是规范上的权威，好吗？
what I mean, I'm the authoritative on the spec, okay?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：[笑]&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：别人接了电话
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [LAUGH] &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Somebody else answered
这个问题，他们完全错了。
the question, and they were completely wrong.
完全错误。
Just 100% totally wrong.
我不觉得，我不喜欢那个人，人们会犯错，
I don't feel, I'm not like down on that person, people make mistakes,
他们不懂东西。
they don't understand stuff.
但这里是如此令人沮丧的是，绿色复选标记和超过4000次上传。
But here's what was so demoralizing, the green check mark and over 4000 uploads.
即使当我发布我的小回复时，现在也有17个上传了，
Even when I post my little answer there is now like 17 uploads,
它永远不会被任何人看到。
it's never going to get seen by anybody.
所以你不能总是相信你在足球列表上读到的东西。
So you can't always trust what you read on Soccer List.
抱歉我说了这么小的离题，好吗？
Sorry for that little digression, okay?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：我们可以帮助你。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: We can help you.
我们都可以支持你。
We can all upvote you.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的，我们可以再获得100票[笑]。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah, we can get 100 more votes [LAUGH].
这不会让我达到4000。
It's not gonna get me to 4000.
但不管怎样，所以，我想说的是有很多问题
But anyway, so, the point that I was making is there's lots of questions where
人们会问关于吊装这件事的问题，他们会说我
people will ask questions about this whole hoisting thing, and they'll say I'm
沮丧，因为这似乎不是正确的工作方式或我是什么。
frustrated because this doesn't seem to work the right way or what am I.
有人会接电话，他们会用吊装，而且
And somebody will answer it and they'll use hoisting, and
它将使不准确永久化。
it will perpetuate inaccuracy.
这并不是说吊装对你没有帮助，而是当你使用吊装时，并且
It is not that hoisting is unhelpful to you, but when you use hoisting, and
你不知道其中的细微差别，你也不知道实际发生了什么，
you don't know the nuances, and you don't know what's actually happening,
然后你就会被误导去思考错误的事情。
then you actually get misled into thinking the wrong thing.
这就是为什么我第一次教你它是如何真正起作用的，而且
Which is why I first taught you ow it really works, and
我们是如何回到更速记的定义，因为装备了
how we're circling back to the more shorthand definition, because armed with
这两个，你可以确保在未来你不会被弄糊涂。
both of those, you can make sure in the future that you don't get confused.
但是只有提升的武装，它只需要几行代码
But armed only with hoisting, it only takes a few lines of code for
让我迷惑一个开发者。
me to confuse a developer.
所以不是这样的，这些都是向上移动的，
So it is not the case that these get moved up,
就像不是重新分配功能的情况一样。
just like it is not the case that functions get reassigned.
这个代码，如果我们试图找出它的作用，
This code, if we were trying to figure out what it did,
我们会说根据吊装，这就是它所做的。
we would say according to hoisting, that this is what it did.
它首先移动了函数，然后移动了变量声明，然后
It moved the function first, and then it moved the variable declaration, and
然后它执行了。
then it executed.
出于完全相同的原因，它不会丢失变量，也不会丢失函数。
For the exact same reason it doesn't lose variables, it doesn't lose functions.
它在第一次传递期间处理它们，然后执行。
It handle them during the first pass, and then it execute.
然而，在这张幻灯片上有一个重要的区别，
There is, however, and important distinction to be made here on this slide,
这是函数声明和函数表达式之间的区别。
which is the difference between a function declaration and a function expression.
当我们讨论错误函数时，你们中的许多人都在问，嘿，好吧，
A number of you were asking when we were talking about error functions, hey well,
如果我只是将我最喜欢的错误函数赋给一个变量，这不是很好吗？
isn't it okay if I just assign my favorite loving error function to a variable?
可以吗？
Is it okay?
是啊。会有用吗？
Yes. Will it work?
这要看情况。
It depends.
在这个特定的示例中，我们有一些函数必须移到顶部，但是
In this particular example, we have the functions having to move to the top, but
注意第9行上的函数赋值发生了什么，
notice what happened to the function assignment on line 9,
它仍然只发生在第9行。
it's still only happens on line 9.
这意味着第七行将抛出类型错误。
Which means that line seven is going to throw a type error.
所以换句话说，
So in other words,
要使用仅将其赋值给属性或变量的函数形式，
to use the form of function where you only assign it to properties or variables,
您必须在调用所有函数之前定义它们。
you have to have all of your functions defined before you call them.
有些人喜欢这样。
Some people like that.
事实上，在我超过15年的开发生涯中，
As a matter of fact, for probably more than 15 years of my development career,
我就是这么做的。
I did exactly that.
可能是因为我有像C这样的编程语言的根源。
Probably because I have roots in programming languages like C.
我已经习惯了把我所有的职能都放在最高层的习惯，而且
I got used to the habit of having all my functions at the top, and
我所有的可执行代码都在底部。
all my executable code at the bottom.
有一天，大约五六年前，也许差不多七年前
And one day, about five, six years ago, maybe almost seven years ago at this
点，我有一天才明白，为什么我把我所有的功能都放在了顶端，
point, it just dawned on my one day, why am I putting all my functions at the top,
然后每次我打开这个文件
and then every time I open up this file,
我必须滚动3000行才能找到我的可执行代码？
I've gotta scroll 3,000 lines before I can find my executable code?
为什么我不能把代码放在顶部，所以
Why can't I just put that code at the top, so
我打开文件的时候它就在那里？
it's right there when I open up the file?
代码的作用非常明显。
And it's real obvious what the code does.
如果我需要查看函数，它们仍然存在，但是
If I need to look at the functions, they're still there, but
我想轻松找到可执行代码。
I wanna find the executable code easily.
在底部找到它比在顶部找到它要难得多。
And finding it at the bottom is a lot of harder than finding it at the top.
所以我开始把所有的函数放在任何作用域的底部。
And so I just started putting all the functions at the bottom of any scope.
我不仅在顶级作用域中这样做，而且我也在作用域中这样做。
And not only do I do that in the top scope, but I also do that within scopes.
我将可执行代码放在顶部，然后
I put the executable code at the top, and
我将函数声明放在底部。
I put my function declarations at the bottom.
我利用了函数提升这一事实。
And I take advantage of the fact that functions hoist.
他们升起了，对吧？
They hoist, right?
它们是在编译时获取的，并以这样的方式定义
They are taken at compile time and defined in such a way so
它们可以在作用域中甚至比声明它们时更早地使用。
that they can be used even earlier in the scope than when they've been declared.
所以有很多人说JavaScript的提升
So there are many, many people that say that JavaScript's hoisting
机制是系统中一个糟糕的，设计不佳的，有缺陷的部分。
mechanism is a bad, poorly designed, buggy part of the system.
这就是为什么JavaScript不具备词汇范围语言的资格，因为
And it's why JavaScript doesn't qualify as a lexically scoped language because of
吊装，我们不应该使用它，也不应该依赖它。
hoisting, and we shouldn't use it, and shouldn't rely upon it.
就像大多数事情一样，这要看情况，
And as with most things, it kinda depends,
这取决于你对你想要完成的事情的看法。
it depend on your perspective of what you're trying to accomplish.
有时吊装是不好的，而且
It is sometimes the case that hoisting is bad, and
有时候我觉得这个案子很有用。
sometimes the case I think it's quite useful.